Finding Aid for Emil Lorch Papers 1891-2004
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Emil Lorch Papers 1891-2004 1891-1963
Lorch, Emil, 1870-1963.
Professor of architecture at the University of Michigan; includes correspondence, professional organizational activities files, documentation, photographs, and architectural drawings accumulated during his work with the Michigan Historic Buildings Survey
851726; Aa 2 UAm
18 linear feet
14 oversize folders
Bentley Historical Library University of Michigan
The collection was donated by Lorch's son-in-law Roger Bailey in 1963. Donor no. 4041
The collection is open for research.
Emil Lorch was born in Detroit of German-American parentage on July 21, 1870. He attended schools in Detroit, including the Detroit Museum of Art School, then went to work for the city's architectural offices. He next studied at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1890-1892, then returned to Detroit where he worked and was active in art and museum circles, especially the Detroit School of Art where he taught from 1895 to 1898. He studied in Paris, 1898-1899, and then went to Chicago as general assistant to the director of the Chicago Art Institute, 1899-1901. He was also secretary of the Chicago School of Architecture.
Lorch next attended Harvard University, 1901-1903, where he obtained his M.A. degree in architecture. From 1903 to 1906 he was assistant professor of architecture at Drexel Institute in Philadelphia. In the fall of 1906 he came to the University of Michigan to establish a department of architecture in the College of Engineering. Under his leadership, the department in 1931 was re-established as a separate College of Architecture within the university with Lorch appointed as its first dean.
Lorch was both a teacher and a practicing architect. He designed the Architecture Building at the University of Michigan, the Belle Isle Bridge in Detroit, and the residence of Alex Dow in Barton Hills. He was also professionally involved. Lorch served on the Committee on Education of the American Institute of Architects and was active in the Association of Collegiate Schools of Architecture and the Michigan Society of Architects. During his career, Lorch corresponded with all the leading figures in academic architectural education, including Roy Jones, Warren P. Laird., and J. B. Robinson. He also was a leading figure in the movement for licensing architects in Michigan, 1915-1917, and served nationally in this movement through the 1930s via the A.I.A.'s Committee on Registration.
After his retirement from the university in July 1940, Lorch devoted himself almost entirely to preserving Michigan's historic buildings. This interest had been fired originally by the Historic American Buildings Survey of the 1930s on whose advisory committee he served and whose records (Midwest District) form a part of this collection. He was active in the restoration projects of Mackinac Island and other early Michigan forts; and he cataloged and collected information and pictures about hundreds of historic and contemporary Michigan structures.
Lorch died June 20, 1963.
The collection has been arranged into thirteen series: Biographical/personal; Correspondence; Published Articles; Architectural League of America; University of Michigan School of Architecture; Notes for Lectures and Addresses; American Institute of Architects; Research notes and collected material; Historic American Buildings Survey; Miscellaneous organizational interests; Historic Michigan Buildings; Photographs; and Architectural Drawings.
The Emil Lorch papers are valuable for their documentation of the career of this important architectural educator and for that material about Michigan architecture and historic structures that Lorch accumulated in the course of his professional study and organizational involvement. The collection includes extensive correspondence with many of the country's leading architects, most notably members of the "Chicago School," and architectural educators, and manuscript and photographic documentation resulting from Lorch's involvement with the Michigan Historic Buildings Survey and various restoration projects, including Mackinac Island.
Subjects:
Albion College.; Ann Arbor (Mich.)--Buildings, structures, etc.; Architects.; Architecture.; Belle Isle (Detroit, Mich.); Detroit Edison Company.; Detroit Museum of Art.; Dormitories--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Historic American Buildings Survey.; Historic buildings--Michigan.; Holland (Mich.); Lorch, Emil, 1870-1963.; Mackinac Island (Mich.); Michigan. State Board of Registration for Architects, Professional Engineers, and Land Surveyors.; National Council of Architectural Registration Boards.; Tau Sigma Delta.; University of Michigan--Buildings.; University of Michigan. College of Architecture and Design.; University of Michigan. College of Engineering.; University of Michigan. Library.; University of Michigan. Senate.; University of Michigan--Student housing.; Waldenwoods (Hartland, Mich.); World War, 1914-1918.
Subjects - Visual Material:
Albion (Calhoun County, Mich.); Algonac (Mich.); Allegan (Mich.); Ann Arbor (Mich.)--Buildings, structures, etc.; Ann Arbor (Mich.)--Panoramic views.; Architecture.; Barns.; Battle Creek (Mich.); Bay City (Mich.); Benton Harbor (Mich.); Berrien Springs (Mich.); Blissfield (Mich.); Bloomfield Hills (Mich.); Buchanan (Mich.); Buildings.; Business enterprises.; Cambridge Junction (Mich.); Cassopolis (Mich.); Charlevoix (Mich.); Chelsea (Mich.); Churches.; Climax (Mich.); Clinton (Mich.); Coloma (Mich.); Concord (Mich.); Constantine (Mich.); Courthouses.; Dearborn (Mich.); Detroit (Mich.)--Buildings, structures, etc.; Detroit (Mich.)--Panoramic views.; Dexter (Mich.); Dixboro (Mich.); Drayton Plains (Mich.); Dwellings.; East Grand Rapids (Mich.); East Lansing (Mich.); Eastmanville (Mich.); Farmington (Mich.); Fayette (Mich.); Fenton (Mich.); Flint (Mich.); Fort Wilkins (Mich.); Goodrich (Mich.); Grand Island (Alger County, Mich.); Grand Rapids (Mich.); Grass Lake (Mich.); Grindstone City (Mich.); Grosse Ile (Mich.); Grosse Pointe (Mich.); Harbor Springs (Mich.); Hartland (Mich.); Highland Park (Mich.); Hillsdale (Mich.); Holland (Mich.); Hotels and taverns.; Huron Mountain Club.; Irish Hills (Mich.); Ithaca (Mich.); Jonesville (Mich.); Kalamazoo (Mich.); Lamont (Mich.); Lansing (Mich.); Lapeer (Mich.); Log cabins.; Mackinaw City (Mich.); Mackinac Island (Mich.); Macon (Mich.); Manchester (Mich.); Manistee (Mich.); Maple Rapids (Mich.); Marquette (Mich.); Marshall (Mich.); Mason, George DeWitt, b. 1856.; Mendon (Mich.); Monroe (Mich.); Mount Clemens (Mich.); Munising (Mich.); Muskegon (Mich.); Niles (Mich.); Northville (Mich.); Otsego (Mich.); Paris (Mich.); Paw Paw (Mich.); Petoskey (Mich.); Plainwell (Mich.); Pontiac (Mich.); Presque Isle (Mich.); Port Hope (Mich.); Port Huron (Mich.); Royal Oak (Mich.); Rushton (Mich.); Saginaw (Mich.); Saint Clair (Mich.); Saint Joseph (Mich.); Salem (Mich.); Saline (Mich.); Saugatuck (Mich.); Sault Sainte Marie (Mich.); Sharon (Mich.); South Lyon (Mich.); Spring Arbor (Mich.); Springville (Mich.); Sylvan Center (Mich.); Tecumseh (Mich.); Tipton (Mich.); Utica (Mich.); Washington (Mich.); White Pigeon (Mich.); Whitneyville (Mich.); Ypsilanti (Mich.)
Contributors:
American Institute of Architects.; Angell, James Burrill, 1829-1916.; Architectural League of America.; Association of Collegiate Schools of Architects.; Baldwin, Frank Conger, 1869-1945.; Barbour, Levi L. (Levi Lewis), 1840-1925.; Booth, Henry Scripps, 1897-1988; Burnham, Daniel Hudson, 1846-1912.; Burton, Marion Le Roy, 1874-1925.; Chandler, F. W. (Francis Ward), 1844-1926.; Copeland, Royal S. (Royal Samuel), 1868-1938.; Cret, Paul Philippe, 1876-1945.; Crouse, John Robert, 1874-1946.; Elmslie, George Grant, 1871-1952.; Fairbanks, Avard T. (Avard Tennyson), 1897-1987.; Ferris, Woodbridge N., 1853-1928.; Fitzgerald, Frank Dwight, 1885-1939.; French, William M. R. (William Merchant Richardson), 1843-1914.; Gilbert, Cass, 1859-1934.; Gomberg, Moses, 1866-1947.; Goodhue, Bertram Grosvenor, 1869-1924.; Hamlin, Talbot, 1889-1956.; Hutchins, Harry B. (Harry Burns), 1847-1930.; Ives, Percy.; James, Edmund J. (Edmund Janes), 1855-1925.; Jones, Roy D.; Kahn, Albert, 1869-1942.; Kimball, Fiske, 1888-1955.; Laird, Warren Powers, 1861-1948.; Lawrence, William Henry, b. 1868.; McKim, Mead & White.; McKim, Charles Follen, 1847-1909.; Maroti, Geza.; Marquand, Allan, 1853-1924.; Mason, George D., b. 1856.; Moon, Charles H.; Mumford, Lewis, 1895-1990.; Murphy, Frank, 1890-1949.; Pond, Irving K. (Irving Kane), 1857-1939.; Pritchett, Henry Smith, 1857-1939.; Rindge, Warren.; Robinson, John Beverley, 1853-; Ross, Denman Waldo, 1853-1935.; Saarinen, Eliel, 1873-1950.; Sleeper, Albert E., 1862-1934.; Sullivan, Louis H., 1856-1924.; Wallenberg, Raoul.; Warren, Herbert Langford, 1857-1917.; Wilson, Woodrow, 1856-1924.; Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1867-1959.
Genre/Form:
Architectural drawings.; Paintings.; Photographs.
- Biographical/Personal
  The Biographical/Personal series (3 folders) consists of collected biographical information about Lorch and materials that he accumulated about the Lorch family. Some of this material is quite early, dating from 1806, and written in German script.
  - Biographical information and personal miscellaneous (Box 1)
    [1-1]
  - "Emil Lorch and the Education of the Modern Architect", 2004 (Box 1)
  - Lorch family genealogical information (Box 1)
    [1-2]
  - Lorch family genealogical volume 1806-circa 1915 (Box 1)
    (manuscript volume largely in German)
    [1-3]
- Correspondence 1891-1962, 9.5 linear feet
  Correspondence is the largest series in the collection. Arranged chronologically, the series includes interchanges between Lorch and his university and professional colleagues. This series also includes items other than correspondence, such as reports, memoranda, and speeches. Because Lorch was in Chicago at the turn-of-the-century, he came to know Louis Sullivan and other members of the "Chicago School" of architecture. Within his collection, there is correspondence with W. M. R. French, director of the Chicago Art Institute as well as some letters from Sullivan himself. More important is Lorch's lifelong correspondence spanning forty years with George Elmslie, intimate associate and colleague of Sullivan and Frank Lloyd Wright, and Lorch's brother-in-law. As Lorch was also a student at M.I.T. and Harvard, Lorch knew and came to correspond with Denman Ross, F.W. Chandler and Warren H. Langford. Lorch's correspondence covers a range of topics, not just matters relating to architecture. For example, there is much lore and information about early 20th century academia, some documentation of the effect of the Great Depression on a vulnerable profession - architecture, the effects of World War I and II on the academic community (especially young people), and official state and professional attempts to save a visible and concrete past via architecture.
  Appended to this finding aid is a selective listing of correspondents and subjects documented in the collection. This listing was prepared soon after the collection came to the library in 1965.
  - 1892-1898 (Box 1)
    [1-4]
  - January-May 1899 (Box 1)
    [1-5]
  - June-December 1899 (Box 1)
    [1-6]
  - 1900 (Box 1)
    [1-7]
  - Undated circa 1901 (Box 1)
    [1-8]
  - January-June 1901 (Box 1)
    [1-9]
  - July-August 1901 (Box 1)
    [1-10]
  - September-October 1901 (Box 1)
    [1-11]
  - November 1901 (Box 1)
    [l-12]
  - December 1901 (Box 1)
    [1-13]
  - January-February 1902 (Box 1)
    [1-14]
  - March-April 1902 (Box 1)
    [1-15]
  - May 1902 (Box 1)
    [1-16]
  - June 1902 (Box 1)
    [1-17]
  - July 1902 (Box 1)
    [l-18]
  - August 1902 (Box 1)
    [1-19]
  - September 1902 (Box 1)
    [l-20]
  - October 1902 (Box 1)
    [1-21]
  - November 1902 (Box 1)
    [l-22]
  - December 1902 (Box 1)
    [1-23]
  - January-February 1903 (Box 1)
    [1-24]
  - March-April 1903 (Box 1)
    [1-25]
  - May-June 1903 (Box 1)
    [1-26]
  - July-August 1903 (Box 1)
    [1-27]
  - September-October 1903 (Box 1)
    [1-28]
  - November-December and 1903 undated (Box 1)
    [1-29]
  - January-February 1904 (Box 1)
    [1-30]
  - March-April 1904 (Box 1)
    [1-31]
  - May-June 1904 (Box 1)
    [1-32]
  - July-August 1904 (Box 1)
    [1-33]
  - September-October 1904 (Box 1)
    [1-34]
  - November-December 1904 (Box 1)
    [1-35]
  - January-February 1905 (Box 1)
    [1-36]
  - March-April 1905 (Box 1)
    [l-37]
  - May-June 1905 (Box 1)
    [l-38]
  - July-August 1905 (Box 1)
    [1-39]
  - September-October 1905 (Box 1)
    [1-40]
  - November 1905 (Box 1)
    [1-41]
  - December 1905 (Box 1)
    [l-42]
  - Undated 1905 (Box 1)
    [1-43]
  - January-May 1906 (Box 1)
    [l-44]
  - June-December 1906 (Box 1)
    [1-45]
  - January-May 1907 (Box 2)
    [2-1]
  - June-August 1907 (Box 2)
    [2-2]
  - September-December 1907 (Box 2)
    [2-3]
  - January-April 1908 (Box 2)
    [2-4]
  - May-July 1908 (Box 2)
    [2-5]
  - August-September 1908 (Box 2)
    [2-6]
  - October-December and 1908 undated (Box 2)
    [2-7]
  - January 1909 (Box 2)
    [2-8]
  - February 1909 (Box 2)
    [2-9]
  - March 1909 (Box 2)
    [2-10]
  - April 1909 (Box 2)
    [2-11]
  - May 1909 (Box 2)
    [2-12]
  - June-July 1909 (Box 2)
    [2-13]
  - August-September 1909 (Box 2)
    [2-14]
  - October 1909 (Box 2)
    [2-15]
  - November-1-15 1909 (Box 2)
    [2-16]
  - November 16-30, 1909 (Box 2)
    [2-17]
  - December 1909 (Box 2)
    [2-18]
  - Undated 1909 (Box 2)
    [2-19]
  - January-March 1910 (Box 2)
    [2-20]
  - April-May 1910 (Box 2)
    [2-21]
  - June-September 1910 (Box 2)
    [2-22]
  - October-December 1910 (Box 2)
    [2-23]
  - January-February 1911 (Box 2)
    [2-24]
  - March-May 1911 (Box 2)
    [2-25]
  - June-September 1911 (Box 2)
    [2-26]
  - October-December 1911 (Box 2)
    [2-27]
  - January-March 1912 (Box 2)
    [2-28]
  - April 1912 (Box 2)
    [2-29]
  - May 1912 (Box 2)
    [2-30]
  - June-July 1912 (Box 2)
    [2-31]
  - August 1912 (Box 2)
    [2-32]
  - September 1912 (Box 2)
    [2-33]
  - October 1912 (Box 2)
    [2-34]
  - November 1912 (Box 2)
    [2-35]
  - December 1912, 1912 undated (Box 2)
    [2-36]
  - January-February 1913 (Box 2)
    [2-37]
  - March 1913 (Box 2)
    [2-38]
  - April-June 1913 (Box 2)
    [2-39]
  - July 1913 (Box 2)
    [2-40]
  - August 1913 (Box 2)
    [2-41]
  - September-October 1913 (Box 2)
    [2-42]
  - November-December 1913, 1913 undated (Box 2)
    [2-43]
  - January-March 1914 (Box 2)
    [2-44]
  - April-June 1914 (Box 2)
    [2-45]
  - July-August 1914 (Box 2)
    [2-46]
  - September-December 1914, 1914 undated (Box 2)
    [2-47]
  - January-March 1915 (Box 2)
    [2-48]
  - April-May 1915 (Box 2)
    [2-49]
  - June-July 1915 (Box 2)
    [2-50]
  - August 1915 (Box 2)
    [2-51]
  - September-October 1915 (Box 2)
    [2-52]
  - November-December 1915, 1915 undated (Box 2)
    [2-53]
  - January-February 1916 (Box 2)
    [2-54]
  - March-April 1916 (Box 2)
    [2-55]
  - May-June 1916 (Box 2)
    [2-56]
  - July-August 1916 (Box 2)
    [2-57]
  - September-October 1916 (Box 2)
    [2-58]
  - November-December 1916 (Box 2)
    [2-59]
  - January-March 1917 (Box 3)
    [3-1]
  - April-June 1917 (Box 3)
    [3-2]
  - July-September 1917 (Box 3)
    [3-3]
  - October-December and 1917 undated (Box 3)
    [3-4]
  - January-April 1918 (Box 3)
    [3-5]
  - May-September 1918 (Box 3)
    [3-6]
  - October-December 1918 (Box 3)
    [3-7]
  - January-March 1919 (Box 3)
    [3-8]
  - April-July 1919 (Box 3)
    [3-9]
  - August-October 1919 (Box 3)
    [3-10]
  - November-December and undated (Box 3)
    [3-11]
  - January-April 1920 (Box 3)
    [3-12]
  - May-September 1920 (Box 3)
    [3-13]
  - October-November 1920 (Box 3)
    [3-14]
  - December and 1920 undated (Box 3)
    [3-15]
  - January-April 1921 (Box 3)
    [3-16]
  - May-September 1921 (Box 3)
    [3-17]
  - October-December 1921 (Box 3)
    [3-18]
  - January-September 1922 (Box 3)
    [3-19]
  - October-December 1922 (Box 3)
    [3-20]
  - Undated 1922 (Box 3)
    [3-21]
  - January-March 1923 (Box 3)
    [3-22]
  - April-May 1923 (Box 3)
    [3-23]
  - January-July 1923 (Box 3)
    [3-24]
  - August-December 1923 (Box 3)
    [3-25]
  - Undated 1923 (Box 3)
    [3-26]
  - January-April 1924 (Box 3)
    [3-27]
  - May-June 1924 (Box 3)
    [3-28]
  - July-August 1924 (Box 3)
    [3-29]
  - September-October 1924 (Box 3)
    [3-30]
  - November-December and 1924 undated (Box 3)
    [3-31]
  - January-March 1925 (Box 3)
    [3-32]
  - April-May 1925 (Box 3)
    [3-33]
  - June-July 1925 (Box 3)
    [3-34]
  - August-September 1925 (Box 3)
    [3-35]
  - October-November 1925 (Box 3)
    [3-36]
  - December and 1925 undated (Box 3)
    [3-37]
  - January-March 1926 (Box 3)
    [3-38]
  - April-May 1926 (Box 3)
    [3-39]
  - June-August 1926 (Box 3)
    [3-40]
  - September 1926 (Box 3)
    [3-41]
  - October-November 1926 (Box 3)
    [3-42]
  - December and 1926 undated (Box 3)
    [3-43]
  - January-February 1927 (Box 3)
    [3-44]
  - March 1927 (Box 3)
    [3-45]
  - April 1927 (Box 3)
    [3-46]
  - May 1927 (Box 3)
    [3-47]
  - June-August 1927 (Box 3)
    [3-48]
  - September-December 1927 (Box 3)
    [3-49]
  - Undated 1927 (Box 3)
    [3-50]
  - January-February 1928 (Box 3)
    [3-51]
  - March-April 1928 (Box 3)
    [3-52]
  - May-July 1928 (Box 3)
    [3-53]
  - August-October 1928 (Box 3)
    [3-54]
  - November-December 1928 (Box 3)
    [3-55]
  - Undated 1928 (Box 3)
    [3-56]
  - January-February 1929 (Box 3)
    [3-57]
  - March 1929 (Box 3)
    [3-58]
  - April 1929 (Box 3)
    [3-59]
  - May-July 1929 (Box 3)
    [3-60]
  - August-November 1929 (Box 3)
    [3-61]
  - December and 1929 undated (Box 3)
    [3-62]
  - January 1930 (Box 3)
    [3-63]
  - February 1930 (Box 3)
    [3-64]
  - March 1930 (Box 3)
    [3-65]
  - April-May 1930 (Box 3)
    [3-66]
  - June-September 1930 (Box 3)
    [3-67]
  - October-November 1930 (Box 3)
    [3-68]
  - December and 1930 undated (Box 3)
    [3-69]
  - January 1931 (Box 4)
    [4-1]
  - February 1931 (Box 4)
    [4-2]
  - March 1931 (Box 4)
    [4-3]
  - March (undated) 1931 (Box 4)
    [4-4]
  - April-May 1931 (Box 4)
    [4-5]
  - June-August 1931 (Box 4)
    [4-6]
  - September 1931 (Box 4)
    [4-7]
  - October 1931 (Box 4)
    [4-8]
  - November 1931 (Box 4)
    [4-9]
  - December 1931 (Box 4)
    [4-10]
  - January-February 1932 (Box 4)
    [4-11]
  - March 1932 (Box 4)
    [4-12]
  - April 1932 (Box 4)
    [4-13]
  - May-July 1932 (Box 4)
    [4-14]
  - August-September 1932 (Box 4)
    [4-15]
  - October 1932 (Box 4)
    [4-16]
  - November-December 1932 (Box 4)
    [4-17]
  - Undated 1932 (Box 4)
    [4-18]
  - January-March 1933 (Box 4)
    [4-19]
  - April-June 1933 (Box 4)
    [4-20]
  - July-December and 1933 undated (Box 4)
    [4-21]
  - January-March 1934 (Box 4)
    [4-22]
  - April-July 1934 (Box 4)
    [4-23]
  - August-December and 1934 undated (Box 4)
    [4-24]
  - January-March 1935 (Box 4)
    [4-25]
  - April-July 1935 (Box 4)
    [4-26]
  - August-November 1935 (Box 4)
    [4-27]
  - December and 1935 undated (Box 4)
    [4-28]
  - January-February 1936 (Box 4)
    [4-29]
  - March-April 1936 (Box 4)
    [4-30]
  - May 1936 (Box 4)
    [4-31]
  - June 1936 (Box 4)
    [4-32]
  - July 1936 (Box 4)
    [4-33]
  - August-September 1936 (Box 4)
    [4-34]
  - October 1936 (Box 4)
    [4-35]
  - November 1936 (Box 4)
    [4-36]
  - December 1936 (Box 4)
    [4-37]
  - Undated 1936 (Box 4)
    [4-38]
  - January 1937 (Box 4)
    [4-39]
  - February 1937 (Box 4)
    [4-40]
  - March 1937 (Box 4)
    [4-41]
  - April 1-15, 1937 (Box 4)
    [4-42]
  - April 16-30, 1937 (Box 4)
    [4-43]
  - May 1-15, 1937 (Box 4)
    [4-44]
  - May 16-31, 1937 (Box 4)
    [4-45]
  - June 1937 (Box 4)
    [4-46]
  - July 1937 (Box 4)
    [4-47]
  - August 1937 (Box 4)
    [4-48]
  - September 1937 (Box 4)
    [4-49]
  - October 1937 (Box 4)
    [4-50]
  - November 1937 (Box 4)
    [4-51]
  - December 1937 (Box 4)
    [4-52]
  - Undated 1937 (Box 4)
    [4-53]
  - January 1938 (Box 5)
    [5-1]
  - February 1938 (Box 5)
    [5-2]
  - March 1938 (Box 5)
    [5-3]
  - April 1938 (Box 5)
    [5-4]
  - May 1938 (Box 5)
    [5-5]
  - June 1938 (Box 5)
    [5-6]
  - July 1938 (Box 5)
    [5-7]
  - August 1938 (Box 5)
    [5-8]
  - September 1938 (Box 5)
    [5-9]
  - October 1938 (Box 5)
    [5-10]
  - November 1938 (Box 5)
    [5-11]
  - December and 1938 undated (Box 5)
    [5-12]
  - January-February 1939 (Box 5)
    [5-13]
  - March-April 1939 (Box 5)
    [5-14]
  - May 1939 (Box 5)
    [5-15]
  - June 1939 (Box 5)
    [5-16]
  - July-August 1939 (Box 5)
    [5-17]
  - September 1939 (Box 5)
    [5-18]
  - October 1939 (Box 5)
    [5-19]
  - November 1939 (Box 5)
    [15-20]
  - December 1939 (Box 5)
    [5-21]
  - January 1940 (Box 5)
    [5-22]
  - February-March (Box 5)
    [5-23]
  - April 1940 (Box 5)
    [5-24]
  - May 1940 (Box 5)
    [5-25]
  - June 1940 (Box 5)
    [5-26]
  - July-September 1940 (Box 5)
    [5-27]
  - October 1940 (Box 5)
    [5-28]
  - November 1940 (Box 5)
    [5-29]
  - December and 1940 undated (Box 5)
    [5-30]
  - January 1941 (Box 5)
    [5-31]
  - February 1941 (Box 5)
    [5-32]
  - March 1941 (Box 5)
    [5-33]
  - April 1941 (Box 5)
    [5-34]
  - May 1941 (Box 5)
    [5-35]
  - June 1941 (Box 5)
    [5-36]
  - July 1941 (Box 5)
    [5-37]
  - August 1941 (Box 5)
    [5-38]
  - September 1941 (Box 5)
    [5-39]
  - October 1941 (Box 5)
    [5-40]
  - November 1941 (Box 5)
    [5-41]
  - December 1941 (Box 5)
    [5-42]
  - Undated 1941 (Box 5)
    [5-43]
  - January 1942 (Box 6)
    [6-l]
  - February 1942 (Box 6)
    [6-2]
  - March 1942 (Box 6)
    [6-3]
  - April 1942 (Box 6)
    [6-4]
  - May 1942 (Box 6)
    [6-5]
  - June 1942 (Box 6)
    [6-6]
  - July 1942 (Box 6)
    [6-7]
  - August 1942 (Box 6)
    [6-8]
  - September 1942 (Box 6)
    [6-9]
  - October 1942 (Box 6)
    [6-10]
  - November 1942 (Box 6)
    [6-11]
  - December 1942 (Box 6)
    [6-12]
  - January 1943 (Box 6)
    [6-13]
  - February 1943 (Box 6)
    [6-14]
  - March 1943 (Box 6)
    [6-15]
  - April 1943 (Box 6)
    [6-16]
  - May 1943 (Box 6)
    [6-17]
  - June-July 1943 (Box 6)
    [6-18]
  - August-October 1943 (Box 6)
    [6-19]
  - November-December 1943 (Box 6)
    [6-20]
  - January 1944 (Box 6)
    [6-21]
  - February 1944 (Box 6)
    [6-22]
  - March 1944 (Box 6)
    [6-23]
  - April-May 1944 (Box 6)
    [6-24]
  - June-July 1944 (Box 6)
    [6-25]
  - August-September 1944 (Box 6)
    [6-26]
  - October 1944 (Box 6)
    [6-27]
  - November 1944 (Box 6)
    [6-28]
  - December 1944 (Box 6)
    [6-29]
  - Undated 1944 (Box 6)
    [6-30]
  - January 1945 (Box 6)
    [6-31]
  - February 1945 (Box 6)
    [6-32]
  - March 1945 (Box 6)
    [6-33]
  - April-May 1945 (Box 6)
    [6-34]
  - June-July 1945 (Box 6)
    [6-35]
  - August-September 1945 (Box 6)
    [6-36]
  - October-November 1945 (Box 6)
    [6-37]
  - December and 1945 undated (Box 6)
    [6-38]
  - January-February 1946 (Box 6)
    [6-39]
  - March-April 1946 (Box 6)
    [6-40]
  - May-June 1946 (Box 6)
    [6-41]
  - July 1946 (Box 6)
    [6-42]
  - August-September 1946 (Box 6)
    [6-43]
  - October 1946 (Box 6)
    [6-44]
  - November-December and 1946 undated (Box 6)
    [6-45]
  - January 1947 (Box 6)
    [6-46]
  - February 1947 (Box 6)
    [6-47]
  - March 1-15, 1947 (Box 6)
    [6-48]
  - March 16-31, 1947 (Box 6)
    [6-49]
  - April 1947 (Box 6)
    [6-50]
  - May 1947 (Box 6)
    [6-51]
  - June 1947 (Box 6)
    [6-52]
  - July-August 1947 (Box 6)
    [6-53]
  - September-October 1947 (Box 6)
    [6-54]
  - December and 1947 undated (Box 6)
    [6-55]
  - January 1948 (Box 6)
    [6-56]
  - February 1948 (Box 6)
    [6-57]